https://digital-photography-school.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Digital Photography School is operated by  D4 Communications Pty Ltd (“D4”). As such, it is run under D4’s general privacy policy.
D4 understands the importance of protecting your personal information and undertakes to adhere to this privacy policy at all times to ensure your personal information is effectively safeguarded.
What type of personal information we collect
D4 undertakes to collect your personal information only where it is necessary for the purposes of marketing our products and where requested distributing newsletters, licensing our products, updating our products, and responding to sales and technical queries.
In most circumstances this information will be limited to your contact details, including but not limited to your name, address, e-mail address, company, company ABN, company address, your job title and phone numbers. Where orders are made online using credit card details, all information is securely transmitted in an encrypted format to D4.
When do we collect personal information
D4 collects personal information when you complete one of the following actions:
Order products from D4;
Lodge a technical support query regarding D4 products of services;
Participate in D4 promotional activities or surveys;
Where you forward information to us in an email or as a hard copy document; and
Other circumstances where collecting personal information is reasonable and permitted by the Laws of the State of Victoria, Australia.
Use of Cookies and Third Party Advertising
The D4 companies’ web sites may from time to time use cookies. A cookie is a piece of text that is saved to your browser by a web site to enable that website to save certain information to your machine so that it can later be retrieved. We do not use cookies to collect personal information about you. While you may set your browser to not accept cookies from D4 web sites, some functions of the web sites may not be available when cookies are not accepted.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
How we manage personal information
D4 undertakes to take all commercially reasonable steps to ensure that all personal information collected by us is accurate, up-to-date, complete and stored securely.
When your personal information is no longer required for the purposes which D4 uses personal information, all commercially reasonable steps will be undertaken to securely destroy that information.
How will your personal information be used
D4 may use your personal information for any of the following purposes:
Marketing D4 products;
Fulfilling orders for D4 products;
Updating D4 products;
Responding to enquiries about D4 products; and
Fulfil all legal requirements of D4 with respect to your personal information.
D4 considers personal information we collect about you to be confidential and will not disclose such information to third parties except in the following circumstances:
Where you have consented to your personal information being provided to a third party;
Where D4 is required by law to disclose your information; and
Where D4 discloses personal information to the related entities of D4.
Gaining access to your personal information held by D4
Except in circumstances where access to your personal information may be denied by the Privacy Act or other Law of the State of Victoria, Australia, your personal information will be provided to you upon request to D4 Privacy Officer. Please find contact details for our Privacy Officer below.
Correcting your personal information held by D4
D4 appreciates you informing us if you have reason to believe that personal information we hold about you is incorrect, incomplete or not updated.
Privacy office contact details
Should you have any queries in relation to the above or require further information regarding D4’s collection, use and storage of your personal information please do not hesitate to contact our Privacy Officer at: privacy@digital-photography-school.com
California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”)
Under CCPA, Californian residents have the right to declare their preferences on the sale of data for advertising and marketing purposes. If you wish to change your preferences, click this link to launch our preference portal:
Californian residents also have the right to access and/or delete collected data about them. If you wish to invoke either right, please see this link.
We use a third-party to provide monetisation technologies for our site. You can review their privacy and cookie policy here.
Sign up to the weeklydPS NEWSLETTER
Your email
Subscribe
Your email is safe with us.
All of our latest weekly articles
Creative photo challenges
Special offers and discounts
